A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virginia Secretary of Education, 1975-1997.
Library of Virginia
- Secretary's correspondence and subject files (Accession 32651), 1975-1985 (bulk 1982-1984)., Extent: 29 cubic feet (29 boxes)
  - Virginia Community College System - Piedmont Virginia CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Rappahannock CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Southside Virginia CC, 1982-1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Thomas Nelson CC, 1979-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Tidewater CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Virginia Highlands CC, 1981-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Virginia Western CC, 1981-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Wytheville CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Dept. of Education - Correspondence, 1984 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Correspondence, 1984 Apr-May. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Correspondence, 1984 Mar. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Correspondence, 1984 Jan-Feb. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Correspondence, 1983 Dec. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Correspondence, 1983 Oct-Nov. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Correspondence, 1983 Jan-Aug. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Accreditation Standards, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Adopt-A-School Program, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Basic Aid, 1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Basic Aid, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Budget materials, 1982-1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Career Ladders, 1985. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Career Ladders, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Center to Support Public Edcuation, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Changing Jobs Study, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Child Care Facilities, 1982-1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - College Preparatory Curriculum, 1982-1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Compulsory School Attendance, 1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Computers, 1982-1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Composite Index Variables, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Conservation Education, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Cooperative Education, 1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Deaf students, 1982-1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Division of Superintendents, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Emotionally disturbed students, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Employment levels, 1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Employment levels, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - FTE, 1982-1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Foreign Language - Articles and information, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Foreign Language - Business meeting, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - General Assembly, 1983. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Education - Foreign Languate - General, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Foreign Languate Committee Recommendations, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Foreign Language Task Force Meeting, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Foreign Language Task Force, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Foreign Languate International Executive Meeting, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Gifted and Talented, 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Gifted and Talented, 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Grievance procedures, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Guidance, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Handicapped students, 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - High School Dropouts, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Impact Aid, 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Indrect Cost Recoveries, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Instructional computing, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Leases, 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Libraries, 1983-1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Magnet Schools, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Magnet Schools, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Martin, Donald, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Merit Pay Committee, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Merit Pay Committee, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Merit Pay, 1983 Nov-Dec. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Merit Pay, 1983 Aug-Oct. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Merit Pay, 1983 May-July. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Merit Pay, 1983 Jan-May. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Merit Pay for Performance Ratings, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Merit Pay Reports, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Education - Middle School Certification Standards, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Mooney, Evelyn, 1984. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Migrant Education Programs, 1982-1984. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Missions - Functions and roles, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - National Teacher's Exam, 1984. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Non-Educational activities, undated. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Parents to be Teachers, 1984. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Pennsylvania School System, 1984. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Professional Development Conference, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Project Slate, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Proposals and studies, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Reading Month, 1983-1984. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Region IV Superintendents Conference, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Research and evaluation, 1985. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - Scholarships, 1982-1983. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - All Public School Systems (Accomack-Wythe), 1982-1983. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Education - All Public School Systems (Va. Beach-York), 1982-1985. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Schools for the Future, 1982. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - School openings, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Standards of Quality, 1982-1984. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Shakespeare, 1985. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Shingleton, Callie, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - State and Federal funded positions, 1982. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Summer activities, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Teacher Education, 1983. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Teacher preparations programs, 1983. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Teacher certification, 1982. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Teacher salaries, 1982. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Transportation, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Turnkey systems, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Upgrade teachers, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Vocational Education, 1983. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education - Youth Forum, 1982-1983. (Box 7)
  - Colleges and Universities - Christopher Newport College, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Christopher Newport College - Fixed Accountin and Control System, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - George Mason University, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - George Mason University - Budget and money matters, 1982-1983. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - George Mason University - Doctoral in Nursing Science, 1984-1985. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - George Mason University - Institute for Science and Technology, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - George Mason University - Physical Education Building, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - George Mason University - Statistical Information, 1981-1982. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - James Madison University, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - James Madison University - Budget and money matters, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Longwood College, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Longwood College - Faculty salaries, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Longwood College - OCR, 1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Mary Washington College, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Mary Washington College - Budget and money matters, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Mary Washington University - Dormitory regulations, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Mary Washington College - Faculty salaries, 1984-1985. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Mary Washington College - James Monroe Memorial Foundation, undated. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Norfolk State University, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Norfolk State University - Budget and money matters, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Norfolk State University - OCR, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Norfolk State University - School of Education, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University, 1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University - Blackwater Zuni Pine Barrens, 1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University - Budget and money matters, 1982-1983. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University - Center for International Programs, 1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University - Cooperative Education Program, 1982-1985. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University - Darden School of Education, 1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University - Investment in Potential, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Old Dominion University - Land acquisition, 1984. (Box 8)
  - Colleges and Universities - Radford University, 1982-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - Radford University - Budgt and money matters, 1982-1985. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - Radford University - Pre-planning justification, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - Radford University - President Dedmon's speech "Scrutinizing Education in the U.S.", 1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - Richard Bland College, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - Richard Bland College - Budget and money matters, 1982-1983. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - Richard Bland College - Financial statement, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia, 1982-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Admissions, 1982-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Alumni Association, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Articles, clippings and speeches, 1982-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Athletics, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Budget and money matters, 1982-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Budget, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Carter C. Wilson Institute, 1982-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Consolidated Salary Authorization, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Continuing Education, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Counselor Education, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Delta Kappa Gamma, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - State Information Committee, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Cypriot Pottery, 1982-1983. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Dimberg, Ronald, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Educateur Program, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Equal Opportunity Programs, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Faculty salary and benefits, 1982-1983. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - French, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - General Assebmly, 1985. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1982-1983. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1982-1985. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Health Services, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Hospital, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Hospital, 1982-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Hospital, 1982-1983. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Institute of Government, 1983-1984. (Box 9)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - School of Architecture, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - School of Education, 1982-1985. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Jefferson Scholars, 1985. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Jefferson Society, 1984-1985. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - James O. McDowelle School of Engineering, 1982. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Johnson Property, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Law School, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - MASDA, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Medical Alumni meetings, 1982-1985. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Pre-planning justification, 1985. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Procurement review, 1982. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Provost, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Russell Estate, Mineral rights, 1982. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Sprigg Lane, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Special Education, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Student Affairs, 1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Student Council, 1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Tayloe Murphy Institute, 1983-1985. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - Urban Land Institute of Washington, DC, 1985. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - VARC, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia - VARC Governor's Conference on Travel and Tourism, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University - Budget and money matters, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University - Council of Presidents, 1982. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University - Community and Public Affairs, School of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University - Conferences, Workshops and Invitations, 1982. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University - Education, School of, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University - Industry / University Relationships, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University - Medical College of Virginia, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Commonwealth University - T. Edward Temple Faculty Executive Exchange Program, 1982. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Military Institute, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Military Institute - Budget and money matters, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Military Institute - OCR, 1984. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1983-1985. (Box 10)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1982. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Admissions Office, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Agriculture, College of, 1982-1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Budget and money matters, 1983-1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Budget and money matters, 1982. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Humanities Conference, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - IBM, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Langley Research Center, 1982. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Microcomputers, 1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Education, School of, 1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Engineering, School of, 1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia State University, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia State University - Audit, 1982. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia State University - Education Association, 1983-1985. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia State University - VELA, 1981-1983. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia State University - OCR, 1982. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia State University - Tom Law's resignation / Presidential search, 1982. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - The College of William and Mary, 1982-1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - The College of William and Mary - Annual report, 1983-1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - The College of William and Mary - Audit reports, 1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - The College of William and Mary - Budget and money matters, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - The College of William and Mary - Articles, clippings and writings, 1982-1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - The College of William and Mary - John Thelin School of Education, 1982-1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - The College of William and Mary - Small laboratories, 1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - The College of William and Mary - Virginia Associated Research Camput, 1983-1984. (Box 11)
  - Colleges and Universities - Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 1983-1984. (Box 11)
  - Agencies - Agency Heads - Education Secretariat, 1982-1983. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Agency regulations, 1981-1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Commission for the Arts, 1981-1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Commission for the Arts, 1983-1984. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Commission for the Arts, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Commission for the Arts - Executive Director, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Jamestown - Yorktown Foundation, 1983-1984. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Jamestown - Yorktown Foundation - Visitation Report, 1984-1985. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Science Museum of Virginia, 1982-1984. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Science Museum of Virginia, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Science Museum of Virginia - Budget and money matters, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Science Museum of Virginia - Budget and money matters, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Science Museum of Virginia - Board, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Science Museum of Virginia - Internship Program, 19. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - State Education Assistance Authority, 1984-1985. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - State Education Assistance Authority, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - State Education Assistance Authority, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - State Education Assistance Authority - Director, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - State Education Assistance Authority - Budget and money matters, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - State Education Assistance Authority - Organization and Management Study, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - State Education Assistance Authority - Relation of SEAA and VELA, 1982-1984. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - State Education Assistance Authority - Reorganization, 1982-1984. (Box 12)
  - Agencies - Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1984. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1982. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Education Loan Authority - Board of Visitors, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Education Loan Authority - Budget and money matters, 1982. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1982-1985. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1982. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1981. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - Audit, 1982-1984. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - Budget and money matters, 1982-1983. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - Project Plan for Organization and Staffing Study, 1982. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - Storage needs, 1982. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - Trustees, 1982. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia State Library, 1984. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia State Library, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia State Library - Affirmative Action Program, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia State Library - Human Services Information and Referral, 1984. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia State Library - Library Networking, 1983. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia State Library - Pre-planning Justification, 1985. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia State Library - Management Review, 1984. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Truck and Ornamental Research Station, 1982-1985. (Box 13)
  - Agencies - Virginia Truck and Ornamental Research Station - Budget and money matters, 1981-1983. (Box 13)
  - A - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 14)
  - Abramson, Neil, 1982. (Box 14)
  - Academy for Educational Development, Inc., 1982-1983. (Box 14)
  - Addendum Proposals, 1982-1984. (Box 14)
  - Administrative Managerial Society (Bob Ball), 1982. (Box 14)
  - Adult Education, 1983. (Box 14)
  - Adult Education Association of Virginia, 1982. (Box 14)
  - Aerospace Research Corporation, 1983. (Box 14)
  - Agency Realignment, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Aging, Dept. for the, 1983. (Box 14)
  - Agricultural Education, 1983. (Box 14)
  - Alliance for Arts Education, Virginia, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Alumni Associations, 1982. (Box 14)
  - Amendments - General, 1985. (Box 14)
  - Amendments - Agencies, 1985. (Box 14)
  - Amendments - Exhibits, 1984. (Box 14)
  - Amendments - Colleges and Universities, 1985. (Box 14)
  - American African Education Foundation, 1982-1983. (Box 14)
  - American Association of Community and Junior Colleges, 1982-1982. (Box 14)
  - American Association of Counseling and Development, 1983. (Box 14)
  - American Association of School Administrators, 1982-1983. (Box 14)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1982-1983. (Box 14)
  - American College Personnel Association, 1983. (Box 14)
  - American Council on Education, 1982. (Box 14)